<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><resources xmlns:xliff="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2">
  <string name="btn_continue">[Çöñţîñûé one]</string>
  <string name="btn_got_it">[Ĝöţ îţ one]</string>
  <string name="btn_turn_on">[Ţûŕñ öñ one]</string>
  <string name="btn_turn_off">[Ţûŕñ öƒƒ one]</string>
  <string name="btn_not_now">[Ñöţ ñöŵ one]</string>
  <string name="btn_cancel">[Çåñçéļ one]</string>
  <string name="btn_delete_status">[Ðéļéţé šţåţûš one two]</string>
  <string name="btn_delete">[Ðéļéţé one]</string>
  <string name="btn_share_this_app">[Šĥåŕé ţĥîš åþþ one two]</string>
  <string name="btn_no_go_back">[Ñö, ĝö бåçķ one two]</string>
  <string name="btn_yes_continue">[Ýéš, çöñţîñûé one two]</string>
  <string name="btn_share_positive">[Šĥåŕé ÇÖVÎÐ-19 ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ one two three four five six]</string>
  <string name="btn_done">[Ðöñé one]</string>
  <string name="btn_back">[Бåçķ one]</string>
  <string name="btn_save">[Šåvé one]</string>
  <string name="btn_discard">[Ðîšçåŕð one]</string>
  <string name="btn_verify">[Véŕîƒý one]</string>
  <string name="learn_more">[Ļéåŕñ möŕé one two]</string>
  <string name="home_tab_exposures_text">[Éxþöšûŕé one]</string>
  <string name="home_tab_notify_text">[Ñöţîƒý öţĥéŕš one two]</string>
  <string name="home_tab_settings_text">[Šéţţîñĝš one]</string>
  <string name="notification_channel_name">[Þöššîбļé ÇÖVÎÐ-19 éxþöšûŕé one two three]</string>
  <string name="notification_channel_description">[Ĝéţ ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš îƒ ýöû ŵéŕé þöššîбļý éxþöšéð ţö šöméöñé ŵîţĥ ÇÖVÎÐ-19. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
  <string name="navigate_up">[Ĝö бåçķ ţö þŕévîöûš šçŕééñ one two three four five six]</string>
  <string name="onboarding_opt_in_title">[Þéŕmîššîöñš ñééðéð ţö îñšţåļļ åñð öþţîmåļļý ûšé ţĥîš åþþ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
  <string name="onboarding_finish_title">[Çöñţîñûåţîöñ öƒ þéŕmîššîöñš ñééðéð ţö îñšţåļļ åñð öþţîmåļļý ûšé ţĥîš åþþ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
  <string name="onboarding_exposure_notifications_title">[Ţûŕñ öñ Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš one two three four five six seven]</string>
  <string name="onboarding_exposure_notifications_detail">[Ţûŕñ öñ Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš šö ţĥåţ ᐅ%1$sᐊ çåñ ñöţîƒý ýöû îƒ ýöû\'vé бééñ ñéåŕ šöméöñé ŵĥö ŕéþöŕţéð ĥåvîñĝ ÇÖVÎÐ-19.
    \ñ\ñÝöûŕ þĥöñé ûšéš Бļûéţööţĥ ţö šéçûŕéļý çöļļéçţ åñð šĥåŕé ŕåñðöm ÎÐš ŵîţĥ öţĥéŕ þĥöñéš ţĥåţ åŕé ñéåŕбý.
    \ñ\ñŢĥé ðåţé, ðûŕåţîöñ, åñð šîĝñåļ šţŕéñĝţĥ åššöçîåţéð ŵîţĥ åñ éxþöšûŕé ŵîļļ бé šĥåŕéð ŵîţĥ ţĥé åþþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight twentynine thirty thirtyone thirtytwo thirtythree thirtyfour thirtyfive thirtysix thirtyseven thirtyeight thirtynine]</string>
  <string name="onboarding_metrics_title">[Ĥéļþ måķé ţĥîš åþþ бéţţéŕ one two three four five six]</string>
  <string name="onboarding_metrics_subtitle">[Šĥåŕé åþþ ûšåĝé &amp; þéŕƒöŕmåñçé ðåţå ŵîţĥ Ĝööĝļé one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
  <string name="onboarding_metrics_detail">[Ţö ĥéļþ måîñţåîñ åñð îmþŕövé ţĥé åþþ, šömé ļîmîţéð ðé-îðéñţîƒîéð ðåţå åбöûţ åþþ þéŕƒöŕmåñçé åñð ûšåĝé îš šĥåŕéð ŵîţĥ Ĝööĝļé. Ţĥîš ðåţå ðöéš ñöţ îðéñţîƒý ýöû. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree]</string>
  <string name="onboarding_confirm_later_title">[Ķééþ Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñ ţûŕñéð öƒƒ¿ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
  <string name="onboarding_confirm_later_detail">[Ûñţîļ Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš åŕé ţûŕñéð öñ, ýöû ŵöñ’ţ бé ñöţîƒîéð öƒ þöššîбļé éxþöšûŕé ţö ÇÖVÎÐ-19 one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen]</string>
  <string name="no_recent_exposure_subtitle">[Ñö ŕéçéñţ éxþöšûŕéš one two three]</string>
  <string name="notifications_enabled_info">[Ýöû çûŕŕéñţļý ĥåvé ñö ŕéþöŕţéð ÇÖVÎÐ-19 éxþöšûŕé ŕîšķ. Ýöû\’ļļ бé ñöţîƒîéð îƒ šöméöñé ýöû ŵéŕé ñéåŕ ŕéþöŕţš å þöšîţîvé ÇÖVÎÐ-19 ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone]</string>
  <string name="exposure_notifications_are_turned_off">[Éxþöšûŕé ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš åŕé ţûŕñéð öƒƒ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
  <string name="turn_on_exposure_notifications_action">[Ţûŕñ öñ Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš one two three four five six seven]</string>
  <string name="recent_exposures_subtitle">[Ŕéçéñţ éxþöšûŕé one two]</string>
  <string name="exposure_details_status_subtitle">[Šţåţûš one]</string>
  <string name="exposure_details_status_exposure">[Þöššîбļé ÇÖVÎÐ-19 éxþöšûŕé one two three]</string>
  <string name="exposure_details_date_exposed_subtitle">[Þöššîбļé éxþöšûŕé ðåţé one two three]</string>
  <string name="exposure_details_expiring_subtitle">[Éxþöšûŕé ŕéþöŕţš åŕé šţöŕéð ƒöŕ 14 ðåýš ƒŕöm ţĥé ðåţé öƒ éxþöšûŕé one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
  <string name="exposure_details_learn_more">[Ļéåŕñ möŕé one two]</string>
  <string name="exposure_details_new_badge">[Ñéŵ one]</string>
  <string name="share_test_result_title">[Þŕöţéçţ ýöûŕ çömmûñîţý, šĥåŕé ýöûŕ ÇÖVÎÐ-19 ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
  <string name="share_test_result_description">[Šĥåŕîñĝ ýöûŕ ÇÖVÎÐ-19 ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ, éšþéçîåļļý îƒ ýöû ĥåvé ţéšţéð þöšîţîvé, ŵîļļ ĥéļþ ñöţîƒý öţĥéŕš ŵĥö måý ĥåvé бééñ éxþöšéð. Îţ ŵîļļ ļéţ öţĥéŕš îñ ýöûŕ çömmûñîţý möñîţöŕ ƒöŕ šýmþţömš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive]</string>
  <string name="test_result_subtitle">[ÇÖVÎÐ-19 Šţåţûš one two]</string>
  <string name="test_result_type_confirmed">[ÇÖVÎÐ-19 Þöšîţîvé one two three]</string>
  <string name="test_result_type_likely">[ÇÖVÎÐ-19 Ļîķéļý one two]</string>
  <string name="test_result_type_negative">[ÇÖVÎÐ-19 Ñéĝåţîvé one two three]</string>
  <string name="positive_test_result_status_shared">[Šĥåŕéð one]</string>
  <string name="positive_test_result_status_not_shared">[Ñöţ šĥåŕéð one two]</string>
  <string name="notify_turn_on_exposure_notifications_header">[Ţö бé ñöţîƒîéð öƒ þöššîбļé ÇÖVÎÐ-19 éxþöšûŕé &amp; šĥåŕé ýöûŕ ÇÖVÎÐ-19 ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ, ţûŕñ öñ Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen]</string>
  <string name="share_begin_title">[Ĥéļþ þŕöţéçţ ýöûŕ çömmûñîţý one two three four five six]</string>
  <string name="share_close_title">[Éxîţ ŵîţĥöûţ šĥåŕîñĝ¿ one two three]</string>
  <string name="share_close_detail">[Ýöû çåñ бéšţ ĥéļþ ýöûŕ çömmûñîţý îƒ ýöû šĥåŕé ýöûŕ ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ šööñéŕ. Ĥöŵévéŕ, ţĥé ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ îñƒöŕmåţîöñ ýöû\'vé éñţéŕéð šö ƒåŕ îš šåvéð îñ ţĥé åþþ ƒöŕ ýöû ţö ŕéšûmé éðîţîñĝ ļåţéŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive]</string>
  <string name="btn_resume_later">[Ýéš, éxîţ one two]</string>
  <string name="verify_test_result_title">[Éñţéŕ ÇÖVÎÐ-19 ţéšţ îñƒöŕmåţîöñ one two three four five six seven]</string>
  <string name="enter_your_test_identifier">[Véŕîƒîçåţîöñ çöðé one two three]</string>
  <string name="share_test_identifier_help">[Ţĥîš öñé-ţîmé çöðé îš ûšéð ţö véŕîƒý ýöûŕ ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ &amp; çåñ\'ţ бé ûšéð åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
  <string name="share_test_identifier_verified">[Ýöûŕ çöðé ĥåš бééñ véŕîƒîéð one two three four five six]</string>
  <string name="share_test_identifier_link">[Ļéåŕñ möŕé åţ ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three four]</string>
  <string name="share_onset_title">[Ĥåvé ýöû ĥåð šýmþţömš¿ one two three four five]</string>
  <string name="share_onset_subtitle">[Ĥéļþš ţĥé åþþ ðéţéŕmîñé ŵĥéñ ýöû måý ĥåvé бééñ îñƒéçţîöûš åñð ñöţîƒý ţĥé ŕîĝĥţ þéöþļé öƒ þöššîбļé éxþöšûŕé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen]</string>
  <string name="test_date_label">[Šýmþţöm šţåŕţ ðåţé one two three]</string>
  <string name="share_onset_symptoms">[Ýéš one]</string>
  <string name="share_onset_no_symptoms">[Ñö one]</string>
  <string name="share_onset_no_answer">[Þŕéƒéŕ ñöţ ţö åñšŵéŕ one two three four five]</string>
  <string name="share_travel_title">[Ĥåvé ýöû ţŕåvéļéð îñ ţĥé ļåšţ 14 ðåýš\¿ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
  <string name="share_travel_confirmed">[Ýéš one]</string>
  <string name="share_travel_no_travel">[Ñö one]</string>
  <string name="share_travel_no_answer">[Þŕéƒéŕ ñöţ ţö åñšŵéŕ one two three four five]</string>
  <string name="share_review_title">[Ŕévîéŵ ýöûŕ îñƒöŕmåţîöñ one two three]</string>
  <string name="share_review_status_subtitle">[ÇÖVÎÐ-19 šţåţûš one two]</string>
  <string name="share_review_status_confirmed">[Þöšîţîvé one]</string>
  <string name="share_review_status_likely">[Ļîķéļý one]</string>
  <string name="share_review_status_negative">[Ñéĝåţîvé one]</string>
  <string name="share_review_onset_subtitle">[Šýmþţöm îñƒö one two]</string>
  <string name="share_review_onset_date">[Šýmþţömš ƒŕöm ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three four]</string>
  <string name="share_review_onset_no_symptoms">[Ñö šýmþţömš one two]</string>
  <string name="share_review_onset_no_answer">[Ñöţ åñšŵéŕéð one two]</string>
  <string name="share_review_travel_subtitle">[Ţŕåvéļ ĥîšţöŕý one two]</string>
  <string name="share_review_travel_confirmed">[Ţŕåvéļéð îñ ļåšţ 14 ðåýš one two three four five]</string>
  <string name="share_review_travel_no_travel">[Ñöţ ţŕåvéļéð îñ ļåšţ 14 ðåýš one two three four five six]</string>
  <string name="share_review_travel_no_answer">[Ñöţ åñšŵéŕéð one two]</string>
  <string name="share_confirm_title">[Ţĥåñķ ýöû ƒöŕ šĥåŕîñĝ ýöûŕ ÇÖVÎÐ-19 šţåţûš åñð ĥéļþîñĝ ýöûŕ çömmûñîţý šţåý šåƒé one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
  <string name="not_shared_confirm_title">[ÇÖVÎÐ-19 šţåţûš ñöţ šĥåŕéð one two three four five six]</string>
  <string name="not_shared_confirm_detail">[Ýöûŕ ÇÖVÎÐ-19 šţåţûš ŵåšñ\'ţ šĥåŕéð бûţ îš šåvéð îñ ţĥé åþþ. Ýöû çåñ šĥåŕé öŕ ðéļéţé ýöûŕ šţåţûš åţ åñý ţîmé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen]</string>
  <string name="status_shared_detail_title">[Šĥåŕéð ÇÖVÎÐ-19 šţåţûš one two three]</string>
  <string name="delete_test_result_title">[Ðéļéţé ÇÖVÎÐ-19 ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ¿ one two three four five six]</string>
  <string name="delete_test_result_detail">[Ýöûŕ ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ ðéţåîļš ŵîļļ бé ðéļéţéð ƒŕöm ţĥîš åþþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
  <string name="delete_test_result_confirmed">[Ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ ðéļéţéð one two three]</string>
  <string name="share_error_no_internet">[Çåñ\’ţ šĥåŕé ţéšţ ŕéšûļţš öƒƒļîñé. Çĥéçķ ýöûŕ îñţéŕñéţ çöññéçţîöñ &amp; ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
  <string name="settings_exposure_notifications_subtitle">[Éxþöšûŕé ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš one two three]</string>
  <string name="settings_app_analytics_subtitle">[Åþþ ûšåĝé &amp; þéŕƒöŕmåñçé šĥåŕîñĝ one two three four five six seven]</string>
  <string name="settings_privacy_policy">[Þŕîvåçý þöļîçý one two]</string>
  <string name="settings_legal_terms">[Ļéĝåļ ţéŕmš one two]</string>
  <string name="settings_debug">[Ðéбûĝ möðé one two]</string>
  <string name="settings_share">[Ĥéļþ çöñţåîñ ţĥé šþŕéåð öƒ ÇÖVÎÐ-19. Šĥåŕé ţĥîš åþþ ŵîţĥ ýöûŕ çömmûñîţý åñð ĥéļþ ţĥém þŕöţéçţ ţĥémšéļvéš бéţţéŕ ŵîţĥ þöššîбļé éxþöšûŕé ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo]</string>
  <string name="settings_share_message">[Ĥéļþ ƒîĝĥţ ţĥé šþŕéåð öƒ ÇÖVÎÐ-19 îñ ţĥé çömmûñîţý. Ðöŵñļöåð ţĥé åþþ ĥéŕé: ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
  <string name="settings_open_source">[Öþéñ šöûŕçé ļîçéñšéš one two three]</string>
  <string name="settings_exposure_notifications_on">[Öñ one]</string>
  <string name="settings_exposure_notifications_off">[Öƒƒ one]</string>
  <string name="settings_analytics_on">[Öñ one]</string>
  <string name="settings_analytics_off">[Öƒƒ one]</string>
  <string name="exposure_about_title">[Éxþöšûŕé ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš one two three]</string>
  <string name="exposure_about_toggle">[Ûšé éxþöšûŕé ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš one two three]</string>
  <string name="exposure_about_detail">[Ţûŕñ öñ Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš šö ţĥåţ ᐅ%1$sᐊ çåñ ñöţîƒý ýöû îƒ ýöû’vé бééñ ñéåŕ šöméöñé ŵĥö ŕéþöŕţéð ĥåvîñĝ ÇÖVÎÐ-19.
    \ñ\ñÝöûŕ þĥöñé ûšéš Бļûéţööţĥ ţö šéçûŕéļý çöļļéçţ åñð šĥåŕé ŕåñðöm ÎÐš ŵîţĥ öţĥéŕ þĥöñéš ţĥåţ åŕé ñéåŕбý.
    \ñ\ñŢĥé ðåţé, ðûŕåţîöñ, åñð šîĝñåļ šţŕéñĝţĥ åššöçîåţéð ŵîţĥ åñ éxþöšûŕé ŵîļļ бé šĥåŕéð ŵîţĥ ţĥé åþþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight twentynine thirty thirtyone thirtytwo thirtythree thirtyfour thirtyfive thirtysix thirtyseven thirtyeight thirtynine]</string>
  <string name="exposure_turn_off_title">[Ţûŕñ öƒƒ Éxþöšûŕé ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš¿ one two three four five six seven]</string>
  <string name="exposure_turn_off_detail">[Ýöû ŵöñ\'ţ бé ñöţîƒîéð îƒ ýöû\'ŕé éxþöšéð ţö ÇÖVÎÐ-19 one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
  <string name="app_analytics_title">[Ĥéļþ måķé ţĥîš åþþ бéţţéŕ one two three four five six]</string>
  <string name="app_analytics_toggle">[Šĥåŕé åþþ ûšåĝé &amp; þéŕƒöŕmåñçé ðåţå ŵîţĥ Ĝööĝļé one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
  <string name="app_analytics_detail">[Ţö ĥéļþ måîñţåîñ åñð îmþŕövé ţĥé åþþ, šömé ļîmîţéð, ðé-îðéñţîƒîéð ðåţå åбöûţ åþþ þéŕƒöŕmåñçé åñð ûšåĝé îš šĥåŕéð ŵîţĥ Ĝööĝļé. Ţĥîš ðåţå ðöéš ñöţ îðéñţîƒý ýöû. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree]</string>
  <string name="agency_message_link">[Ļéåŕñ möŕé åţ\ñᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three four]</string>
  <string name="exposure_notifications_are_inactive">[Éxþöšûŕé ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš åŕé îñåçţîvé one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
  <string name="exposure_notifications_currently_inactive">[Éxþöšûŕé ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš åŕé çûŕŕéñţļý îñåçţîvé one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
  <string name="device_settings">[Ðévîçé šéţţîñĝš one two]</string>
  <string name="manage_storage">[Måñåĝé šţöŕåĝé one two]</string>
  <string name="location_off_warning">[Ţö çöñţîñûé ţö ĝéţ þöššîбļé ÇÖVÎÐ-19 éxþöšûŕé ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš &amp; šĥåŕé ýöûŕ ÇÖVÎÐ-19 ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ, ţûŕñ öñ ţĥé ðévîçé ļöçåţîöñ šéţţîñĝ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty]</string>
  <string name="ble_off_warning">[Ţö çöñţîñûé ţö ĝéţ þöššîбļé ÇÖVÎÐ-19 éxþöšûŕé ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš &amp; šĥåŕé ýöûŕ ÇÖVÎÐ-19 ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ, ţûŕñ öñ Бļûéţööţĥ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen]</string>
  <string name="location_ble_off_warning">[Ţö çöñţîñûé ţö ĝéţ þöššîбļé ÇÖVÎÐ-19 éxþöšûŕé ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš &amp; šĥåŕé ýöûŕ ÇÖVÎÐ-19 ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ, ţûŕñ öñ Бļûéţööţĥ åñð ţĥé ðévîçé ļöçåţîöñ šéţţîñĝ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo]</string>
  <string name="storage_low_warning">[Ţö çöñţîñûé ţö ĝéţ Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš &amp; šĥåŕé ýöûŕ ÇÖVÎÐ-19 ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ, ƒŕéé ûþ šţöŕåĝé šþåçé öñ ýöûŕ þĥöñé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen]</string>
  <string name="input_error_onset_date_past">[Ðåţé šĥöûļð öççûŕ ŵîţĥîñ ļåšţ ᐅ%1$sᐊ ðåýš öƒ ţöðåý\’š ðåţé one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
  <string name="input_error_onset_date_future">[Ðåţé öççûŕš îñ ţĥé ƒûţûŕé one two three four five six]</string>
  <string name="network_error_code_invalid">[Ţĥé véŕîƒîçåţîöñ çöðé ðöéšñ’ţ måţçĥ. Ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
  <string name="network_error_code_expired">[Ţĥé véŕîƒîçåţîöñ çöðé îš öûţ öƒ ðåţé. Çöñţåçţ ᐅ%1$sᐊ ƒöŕ å ñéŵ öñé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
  <string name="network_error_server_error">[Šöméţĥîñĝ ŵéñţ ŵŕöñĝ. Ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven]</string>
  <string name="network_error_unsupported_test_type">[Véŕîƒîçåţîöñ çöðé çåñ\’ţ бé ûšéð îñ ţĥîš véŕšîöñ öƒ ţĥé åþþ. Ûþĝŕåðé ţĥé åþþ &amp; ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]</string>
  <string name="share_error">[Ûñåбļé ţö šĥåŕé ţĥé ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ. Ţŕý åĝåîñ ļåţéŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
  <string name="generic_error_message">[Šöméţĥîñĝ ŵéñţ ŵŕöñĝ. Ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven]</string>
  <string name="code_error_already_submitted">[Çöðé ĥåš åļŕéåðý бééñ ûšéð ţö šĥåŕé ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
</resources>
