<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><resources xmlns:xliff="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2">
  <string name="btn_continue">[Çöñţîñûé one]</string>
  <string name="btn_got_it">[Ĝöţ îţ one]</string>
  <string name="btn_turn_on">[Ţûŕñ öñ one]</string>
  <string name="btn_turn_off">[Ţûŕñ öƒƒ one]</string>
  <string name="btn_not_now">[Ñöţ ñöŵ one]</string>
  <string name="btn_cancel">[Çåñçéļ one]</string>
  <string name="btn_delete_status">[Ðéļéţé šţåţûš one two]</string>
  <string name="btn_delete">[Ðéļéţé one]</string>
  <string name="btn_no_go_back">[Ñö, ĝö бåçķ one two]</string>
  <string name="btn_yes_continue">[Ýéš, çöñţîñûé one two]</string>
  <string name="btn_share_positive">[Šĥåŕé ÇÖVÎÐ-19 ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ one two three four five six]</string>
  <string name="btn_done">[Ðöñé one]</string>
  <string name="btn_previous">[Þŕévîöûš one]</string>
  <string name="btn_verify">[Véŕîƒý one]</string>
  <string name="btn_no_thanks">[Ñö ţĥåñķš one two]</string>
  <string name="btn_share">[Šĥåŕé one]</string>
  <string name="btn_close_app">[Çļöšé åþþ one two]</string>
  <string name="learn_more">[Ļéåŕñ möŕé one two]</string>
  <string name="home_tab_settings_text">[Šéţţîñĝš one]</string>
  <string name="notification_channel_name">[Þöššîбļé ÇÖVÎÐ-19 éxþöšûŕé one two three]</string>
  <string name="notification_channel_description">[Ĝéţ ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš îƒ ýöû ŵéŕé þöššîбļý éxþöšéð ţö šöméöñé ŵîţĥ ÇÖVÎÐ-19. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
  <string name="navigate_up">[Ĝö бåçķ ţö þŕévîöûš šçŕééñ one two three four five six]</string>
  <string name="btn_close_label">[Çļöšé one]</string>
  <string name="updated_permission_disabled_notification_title">[Ûñåбļé ţö çĥéçķ ƒöŕ éxþöšûŕéš one two three four five six seven]</string>
  <string name="updated_bluetooth_location_state_notification">[Ţö çöñţîñûé çĥéçķîñĝ ƒöŕ þöššîбļé éxþöšûŕé, ţûŕñ öñ Бļûéţööţĥ åñð ðévîçé ļöçåţîöñ šéţţîñĝ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]</string>
  <string name="updated_bluetooth_state_notification">[Ţö çöñţîñûé çĥéçķîñĝ ƒöŕ þöššîбļé éxþöšûŕé, ţûŕñ öñ Бļûéţööţĥ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
  <string name="updated_location_state_notification">[Ţö çöñţîñûé çĥéçķîñĝ ƒöŕ þöššîбļé éxþöšûŕé, ţûŕñ öñ ðévîçé ļöçåţîöñ šéţţîñĝ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
  <string name="onboarding_opt_in_title">[Þéŕmîššîöñš ñééðéð ţö éñåбļé Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
  <string name="onboarding_finish_title">[Çöñţîñûåţîöñ öƒ þéŕmîššîöñš ñééðéð ţö éñåбļé Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
  <string name="onboarding_exposure_notifications_title">[Ţûŕñ öñ Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš one two three four five six seven]</string>
  <string name="onboarding_exposure_notifications_description">[Ĝéţ ñöţîƒîéð îƒ ýöû\'vé бééñ ñéåŕ šöméöñé ŵĥö ŕéþöŕţéð ĥåvîñĝ ÇÖVÎÐ-19.
    \ñ\ñÝöûŕ þĥöñé ûšéš Бļûéţööţĥ ţö šéçûŕéļý çöļļéçţ åñð šĥåŕé ŕåñðöm ÎÐš ŵîţĥ öţĥéŕ þĥöñéš ţĥåţ åŕé ñéåŕбý.
    \ñ\ñŢĥé ðåţé, ðûŕåţîöñ, åñð šîĝñåļ šţŕéñĝţĥ åššöçîåţéð ŵîţĥ å þöššîбļé éxþöšûŕé ŵîļļ бé ûšéð ţö ðéţéŕmîñé ŵĥéţĥéŕ ýöû ŵîļļ бé ñöţîƒîéð бåšéð öñ þåŕåméţéŕš šéţ бý ýöûŕ þûбļîç ĥéåļţĥ åûţĥöŕîţý.
    \ñ\ñÝöû måý ŕéçéîvé å ñöţîƒîçåţîöñ ţö šĥåŕé å ðîåĝñöšîš ŵîţĥ ýöûŕ ĥéåļţĥ åûţĥöŕîţý îƒ ýöû ĝéţ åñ ŠMŠ ŵîţĥ ýöûŕ ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ. ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight twentynine thirty thirtyone thirtytwo thirtythree thirtyfour thirtyfive thirtysix thirtyseven thirtyeight thirtynine forty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour]</string>
  <string name="onboarding_metrics_title">[Ĥéļþ måķé ţĥîš åþþ бéţţéŕ one two three four five six]</string>
  <string name="onboarding_metrics_subtitle">[Šĥåŕé åþþ ûšåĝé &amp; þéŕƒöŕmåñçé ðåţå ŵîţĥ Ĝööĝļé one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
  <string name="onboarding_metrics_description">[Ţö ĥéļþ måîñţåîñ åñð îmþŕövé ţĥé åþþ, šömé ļîmîţéð ðé-îðéñţîƒîéð ðåţå åбöûţ åþþ þéŕƒöŕmåñçé åñð ûšåĝé îš šĥåŕéð ŵîţĥ Ĝööĝļé. Ţĥîš ðåţå ðöéš ñöţ îðéñţîƒý ýöû. ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree]</string>
  <string name="onboarding_confirm_later_title">[Ķééþ Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš ţûŕñéð öƒƒ¿ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
  <string name="onboarding_confirm_later_detail">[Ûñţîļ Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš îš ţûŕñéð öñ, ýöû ŵöñ’ţ бé ñöţîƒîéð öƒ þöššîбļé éxþöšûŕé ţö ÇÖVÎÐ-19 one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen]</string>
  <string name="no_recent_exposure_indicator">[Ñö ŕéçéñţ éxþöšûŕé one two three]</string>
  <string name="no_recent_exposure_checks">[Åš Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš çĥéçķš ƒöŕ éxþöšûŕéš, ŕéçéñţ çĥéçķš åþþéåŕ бéļöŵ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
  <string name="exposure_notifications_are_turned_off">[Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš îš ţûŕñéð öƒƒ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
  <string name="turn_on_exposure_notifications_action">[Ţûŕñ öñ Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš one two three four five six seven]</string>
  <string name="exposure_details_status_subtitle">[Šţåţûš one]</string>
  <string name="exposure_details_status_exposure">[Þöššîбļé ÇÖVÎÐ-19 éxþöšûŕé one two three]</string>
  <string name="exposure_details_date_exposed_subtitle">[Ðåţé one]</string>
  <string name="exposure_details_expiring_subtitle">[Ýöûŕ ļåţéšţ þöššîбļé éxþöšûŕé ŕémåîñš öñ ţĥîš þåĝé ƒöŕ 2 ŵééķš åƒţéŕ ţĥé ðåţé öƒ éxþöšûŕé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen]</string>
  <string name="exposure_details_learn_more">[Ļéåŕñ möŕé one two]</string>
  <string name="exposure_details_new_badge">[Ñéŵ one]</string>
  <string name="possible_exposures_activity_title">[Þöššîбļé éxþöšûŕé one two three]</string>
  <string name="exposure_details_explanation_link">[Šéé ĥöŵ Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš ŵöŕķš one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
  <plurals name="days_from_start_of_exposure">
    <item quantity="one">[ᐅ%1$dᐊ ðåý åĝö one two three]</item>
    <item quantity="other">[ᐅ%1$dᐊ ðåýš åĝö one two three]</item>
  </plurals>
  <string name="test_result_type_confirmed">[ÇÖVÎÐ-19 þöšîţîvé one two three]</string>
  <string name="test_result_type_likely">[ÇÖVÎÐ-19 ļîķéļý one two]</string>
  <string name="test_result_type_negative">[ÇÖVÎÐ-19 ñéĝåţîvé one two three]</string>
  <string name="positive_test_result_status_shared">[Šĥåŕéð one]</string>
  <string name="positive_test_result_status_not_shared">[Ñöţ šĥåŕéð one two]</string>
  <string name="notify_turn_on_exposure_notifications_header">[Ţö ĝéţ ñöţîƒîéð öƒ þöššîбļé ÇÖVÎÐ-19 éxþöšûŕé, ţûŕñ öñ Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš. ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]</string>
  <string name="using_en_helps_even_if_vaccinated">[Ûšîñĝ ţĥîš šéŕvîçé ĥéļþš ýöû þŕöţéçţ ýöûŕ çömmûñîţý - évéñ îƒ ýöû\'vé бééñ våççîñåţéð. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]</string>
  <string name="share_begin_title">[Ĥéļþ þŕöţéçţ ýöûŕ çömmûñîţý one two three four five six]</string>
  <string name="share_close_title">[Çļöšé ŵîţĥöûţ šĥåŕîñĝ¿ one two three]</string>
  <string name="share_close_detail">[Ţĥé бéšţ ŵåý ýöû çåñ ĥéļþ ýöûŕ çömmûñîţý îš ţö šĥåŕé ýöûŕ ŕéšûļţš åš šööñ åš þöššîбļé. Îƒ ýöû ðö çļöšé ñöŵ ŵîţĥöûţ šĥåŕîñĝ, ýöû çåñ þîçķ ûþ ŵĥéŕé ýöû ļéƒţ öƒƒ îƒ ýöû çĥåñĝé ýöûŕ mîñð ļåţéŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix]</string>
  <string name="btn_resume_later">[Ýéš, çļöšé one two]</string>
  <string name="verify_test_result_title">[Éñţéŕ ýöûŕ véŕîƒîçåţîöñ çöðé one two three four five six]</string>
  <string name="enter_your_test_identifier">[Véŕîƒîçåţîöñ çöðé one two three]</string>
  <string name="share_test_identifier_help">[Ţĥîš öñé-ţîmé çöðé îš ûšéð ţö véŕîƒý ýöûŕ ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
  <string name="share_test_identifier_verified">[Çöðé véŕîƒîéð one two]</string>
  <string name="share_test_identifier_link">[Ļéåŕñ möŕé åţ ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three four]</string>
  <string name="share_onset_title">[Ĥåvé ýöû ĥåð šýmþţömš¿ one two three four five]</string>
  <string name="share_onset_subtitle">[Ĥéļþš ţĥé ĥéåļţĥ åûţĥöŕîţý ðéţéŕmîñé ŵĥéñ ýöû måý ĥåvé бééñ îñƒéçţîöûš åñð ñöţîƒý ţĥé ŕîĝĥţ þéöþļé öƒ þöššîбļé éxþöšûŕé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen]</string>
  <string name="test_date_label">[Ðåţé šýmþţömš šţåŕţéð one two three]</string>
  <string name="share_onset_symptoms">[Ýéš one]</string>
  <string name="share_onset_no_symptoms">[Ñö one]</string>
  <string name="share_onset_no_answer">[Î þŕéƒéŕ ñöţ ţö åñšŵéŕ one two three four five]</string>
  <string name="share_travel_title">[Ĥåvé ýöû ţŕåvéļéð îñ ţĥé ļåšţ 14 ðåýš\¿ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
  <string name="share_travel_confirmed">[Ýéš one]</string>
  <string name="share_travel_no_travel">[Ñö one]</string>
  <string name="share_travel_no_answer">[Î þŕéƒéŕ ñöţ ţö åñšŵéŕ one two three four five]</string>
  <string name="share_review_title">[Ŕévîéŵ ýöûŕ îñƒöŕmåţîöñ one two three]</string>
  <string name="share_review_status_subtitle">[ÇÖVÎÐ-19 šţåţûš one two]</string>
  <string name="share_review_status_confirmed">[Þöšîţîvé one]</string>
  <string name="share_review_status_likely">[Ļîķéļý one]</string>
  <string name="share_review_status_negative">[Ñéĝåţîvé one]</string>
  <string name="share_review_onset_subtitle">[Šýmþţömš one]</string>
  <string name="share_review_onset_date">[Šţåŕţéð ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three]</string>
  <string name="share_review_onset_no_symptoms">[Ñö šýmþţömš one two]</string>
  <string name="share_review_onset_no_answer">[Ñöţ åñšŵéŕéð one two]</string>
  <string name="share_review_travel_subtitle">[Ţŕåvéļ one]</string>
  <string name="share_review_travel_confirmed">[Ŵîţĥîñ ţĥé þåšţ 14 ðåýš one two three four five]</string>
  <string name="share_review_travel_no_travel">[Ñöţ ţŕåvéļéð îñ ļåšţ 14 ðåýš one two three four five six]</string>
  <string name="share_review_travel_no_answer">[Ñöţ åñšŵéŕéð one two]</string>
  <string name="share_confirm_title">[Ţĥåñķ ýöû ƒöŕ šĥåŕîñĝ ýöûŕ ÇÖVÎÐ-19 ŕéšûļţ one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
  <string name="not_shared_confirm_title">[Ýöûŕ ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ ŵåšñ\'ţ šĥåŕéð one two three four five six seven]</string>
  <string name="not_shared_confirm_detail">[Ýöûŕ ÇÖVÎÐ-19 ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ ŵåšñ\'ţ šĥåŕéð. Þļéåšé ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
  <string name="status_shared_detail_title">[Šĥåŕéð ÇÖVÎÐ-19 šţåţûš one two three]</string>
  <string name="delete_test_result_title">[Ðéļéţé ýöûŕ ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ¿ one two three four five]</string>
  <string name="delete_test_result_confirmed">[Ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ ðéļéţéð one two three]</string>
  <string name="share_error_no_internet">[Çåñ\’ţ šĥåŕé ţéšţ ŕéšûļţš öƒƒļîñé. Çĥéçķ ýöûŕ îñţéŕñéţ çöññéçţîöñ &amp; ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
  <string name="share_vaccination_title">[Ĥåvé ýöû бééñ våççîñåţéð åĝåîñšţ Çövîð-19\¿ one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
  <string name="share_vaccination_description">[Ýöû çåñ ĥéļþ évéñ möŕé. Ŵîţĥöûţ šĥåŕîñĝ ýöûŕ îðéñţîţý, ýöû çåñ ĥéļþ ᐅ%1$sᐊ бéţţéŕ ûñðéŕšţåñð ţĥé šþŕéåð öƒ Çövîð-19 бý šĥåŕîñĝ îƒ ýöû\'vé бééñ våççîñåţéð. ᐅ%1$sᐊ ŕéçéîvéš ţĥîš ðåţå îñ åĝĝŕéĝåţé ƒöŕm ţö þŕöţéçţ ýöûŕ þŕîvåçý. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight]</string>
  <string name="share_vaccination_learn_more">[Ļéåŕñ möŕé one two]</string>
  <string name="share_vaccination_vaccinated">[Ýéš, Î\'vé бééñ våççîñåţéð one two three four five six]</string>
  <string name="share_vaccination_not_vaccinated">[Ñö one]</string>
  <string name="share_vaccination_unknown">[Î þŕéƒéŕ ñöţ ţö åñšŵéŕ one two three four five]</string>
  <string name="do_you_have_code_title">[Ðîð ýöû ŕéçéîvé å çöðé¿ one two three four five]</string>
  <string name="do_you_have_code_content">[Îƒ ýöû ţéšţ þöšîţîvé ƒöŕ ÇÖVÎÐ-19, ýöûŕ ĥéåļţĥ åûţĥöŕîţý ûšûåļļý þŕövîðéš å véŕîƒîçåţîöñ çöðé бý þĥöñé öŕ ţéxţ šö ţĥåţ ýöû çåñ šĥåŕé ýöûŕ ŕéšûļţš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo]</string>
  <string name="btn_i_have_code">[Ýéš, Î ĥåvé å çöðé one two three four]</string>
  <string name="btn_i_need_code">[Î ñééð å çöðé one two three]</string>
  <string name="get_verification_code_title">[Ĝéţ å véŕîƒîçåţîöñ çöðé one two three four five]</string>
  <string name="phone_number_prompt">[Þĥöñé ñûmбéŕ one two]</string>
  <string name="phone_number_help">[Å véŕîƒîçåţîöñ çöðé åļļöŵš ýöû ţö šĥåŕé ýöûŕ ţéšţ ŕéšûļţš. Ýöûŕ çöðé ŵîļļ бé šéñţ ţö ţĥé ñûmбéŕ ýöû þŕövîðé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen]</string>
  <string name="phone_number_may_be_stored_help">[Ţö þŕévéñţ þéöþļé ƒŕöm šûбmîţţîñĝ möŕé ţĥåñ öñé ŕéšûļţ, ýöûŕ þĥöñé ñûmбéŕ måý бé ţémþöŕåŕîļý šţöŕéð бý ýöûŕ þûбļîç ĥéåļţĥ åûţĥöŕîţý. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty]</string>
  <string name="test_date_prompt">[Ţéšţ ðåţé one two]</string>
  <string name="test_date_help">[Ţéšţ ðåţé šĥöûļð бé ŵîţĥîñ ţĥé þåšţ 14 ðåýš. one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
  <string name="tested_for_covid_checkbox_text">[Î ĥåvé ŕéçéîvéð å þöšîţîvé ÇÖVÎÐ-19 ţéšţ îñ ţĥé þåšţ 14 ðåýš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
  <string name="btn_send_code">[Šéñð çöðé one two]</string>
  <string name="enter_code_help">[Éñţéŕ ţĥé çöðé šéñţ ţö ýöû бý ᐅ%1$sᐊ. one two three four five six seven]</string>
  <string name="positive_result_already_reported_title">[Ýöû ĥåvé åļŕéåðý ŕéþöŕţéð å ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ ŕéçéñţļý. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
  <string name="positive_result_already_reported_content">[Îƒ ýöû ŵöûļð ļîķé ţö ŕéþöŕţ åñöţĥéŕ ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ, þļéåšé çöñţåçţ ᐅ%1$sᐊ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
  <string name="self_report_bad_code">[Îñvåļîð çöðé. Måķé šûŕé ýöû\'ŕé ûšîñĝ ţĥé šåmé ðévîçé ţö бöţĥ ŕéqûéšţ åñð éñţéŕ ýöûŕ véŕîƒîçåţîöñ çöðé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen]</string>
  <string name="self_report_bad_phone_number">[Çĥéçķ ýöûŕ ñûmбéŕ åñð ţŕý åĝåîñ. ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
  <string name="self_report_code_requested_too_many_times">[Ýöû\'vé måðé ţöö måñý ŕéqûéšţš. Çöñţåçţ ᐅ%1$sᐊ îƒ ýöû šţîļļ ñééð å çöðé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
  <plurals name="self_report_code_already_requested">
    <item quantity="one">[Ýöû\'vé måðé ţöö måñý ŕéqûéšţš. Ýöû çåñ ŕéqûéšţ åñöţĥéŕ çöðé îñ ᐅ%1$dᐊ mîñûţé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</item>
    <item quantity="other">[Ýöû\'vé måðé ţöö måñý ŕéqûéšţš. Ýöû çåñ ŕéqûéšţ åñöţĥéŕ çöðé îñ ᐅ%1$dᐊ mîñûţéš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</item>
  </plurals>
  <string name="notify_others_notification_title">[Ĥéļþ ñöţîƒý öţĥéŕš ŵĥö måý ĥåvé бééñ éxþöšéð one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
  <string name="notify_others_if_result_updated_title">[Ñöţîƒý öţĥéŕ þéöþļé îƒ ýöûŕ ŕéšûļţ ĝéţš ûþðåţéð¿ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
  <string name="notify_others_if_result_updated_content">[ᐅ%1$sᐊ måý šéñð ýöû å šéçöñð çöðé ţö çöñƒîŕm ýöûŕ ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ. Ýöû çåñ åûţömåţîçåļļý ûþðåţé ýöûŕ ÇÖVÎÐ-19 šţåţûš &amp; šĥåŕé åððîţîöñåļ ðåýš öƒ ŕåñðöm ÎÐš ûšîñĝ ţĥîš šéçöñð çöðé, ŵĥîçĥ çåñ ĥéļþ ñöţîƒý öţĥéŕš åбöûţ þöššîбļé éxþöšûŕé. Ýöûŕ îðéñţîţý îš ñöţ šĥåŕéð ŵîţĥ öţĥéŕ þéöþļé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight twentynine thirty thirtyone thirtytwo thirtythree thirtyfour]</string>
  <string name="btn_pre_auth_yes">[Ýéš, Î ŵåñţ ţö ĥéļþ one two three four]</string>
  <string name="btn_pre_auth_no">[Ñö ţĥåñķš one two]</string>
  <string name="thank_you_for_notifying_title">[Ţĥåñķ ýöû ƒöŕ ĥéļþîñĝ one two three four five]</string>
  <string name="thank_you_for_notifying_content">[ᐅ%1$sᐊ ĵûšţ ûþðåţéð ýöûŕ éxþöšûŕé ţîméļîñé åñð måý ĥåvé åļéŕţéð öţĥéŕš öƒ þöššîбļé éxþöšûŕé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]</string>
  <string name="settings_exposure_notifications_subtitle">[Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš one two three]</string>
  <string name="settings_app_analytics_subtitle">[Åþþ ûšåĝé &amp; þéŕƒöŕmåñçé šĥåŕîñĝ one two three four five six seven]</string>
  <string name="settings_privacy_policy">[Þŕîvåçý þöļîçý one two]</string>
  <string name="settings_help_and_support">[Åбöûţ Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš Éxþŕéšš one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
  <string name="settings_legal_terms">[Ļéĝåļ ţéŕmš one two]</string>
  <string name="settings_debug">[Ðéбûĝ möðé one two]</string>
  <string name="settings_share">[Ĥéļþ çöñţåîñ ţĥé šþŕéåð öƒ ÇÖVÎÐ-19. Šĥåŕé ţĥîš åþþ ŵîţĥ ýöûŕ çömmûñîţý åñð ĥéļþ ţĥém þŕöţéçţ ţĥémšéļvéš бéţţéŕ ŵîţĥ þöššîбļé éxþöšûŕé ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo]</string>
  <string name="settings_share_message">[Ĥéļþ ƒîĝĥţ ţĥé šþŕéåð öƒ ÇÖVÎÐ-19 îñ ţĥé çömmûñîţý. Ðöŵñļöåð ţĥé åþþ ĥéŕé: ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
  <string name="settings_open_source">[Öþéñ šöûŕçé ļîçéñšéš one two three]</string>
  <string name="settings_exposure_notifications_on">[Öñ one]</string>
  <string name="settings_exposure_notifications_off">[Öƒƒ one]</string>
  <string name="settings_analytics_on">[Öñ one]</string>
  <string name="settings_analytics_off">[Öƒƒ one]</string>
  <string name="exposure_about_title">[Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš one two three]</string>
  <string name="exposure_about_toggle">[Ûšé Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš one two three]</string>
  <string name="exposure_about_detail">[Ţûŕñ öñ Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš šö ţĥåţ ᐅ%1$sᐊ çåñ ñöţîƒý ýöû îƒ ýöû’vé бééñ ñéåŕ šöméöñé ŵĥö ŕéþöŕţéð ĥåvîñĝ ÇÖVÎÐ-19.
    \ñ\ñÝöûŕ þĥöñé ûšéš Бļûéţööţĥ ţö šéçûŕéļý çöļļéçţ åñð šĥåŕé ŕåñðöm ÎÐš ŵîţĥ öţĥéŕ þĥöñéš ţĥåţ åŕé ñéåŕбý.
    \ñ\ñŢĥé ðåţé, ðûŕåţîöñ, åñð šîĝñåļ šţŕéñĝţĥ åššöçîåţéð ŵîţĥ åñ éxþöšûŕé ŵîļļ бé šĥåŕéð ŵîţĥ ţĥé åþþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight twentynine thirty thirtyone thirtytwo thirtythree thirtyfour thirtyfive thirtysix thirtyseven thirtyeight thirtynine]</string>
  <string name="exposure_turn_off_title">[Ţûŕñ öƒƒ Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš¿ one two three four five six seven]</string>
  <string name="exposure_turn_off_detail">[Ýöû ŵöñ\'ţ бé ñöţîƒîéð îƒ ýöû\'ŕé éxþöšéð ţö ÇÖVÎÐ-19 one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
  <string name="app_analytics_title">[Ĥéļþ måķé ţĥîš åþþ бéţţéŕ one two three four five six]</string>
  <string name="app_analytics_toggle">[Šĥåŕé åþþ ûšåĝé &amp; þéŕƒöŕmåñçé ðåţå ŵîţĥ Ĝööĝļé one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
  <string name="app_analytics_detail">[Ţö ĥéļþ måîñţåîñ åñð îmþŕövé ţĥé åþþ, šömé ļîmîţéð, ðé-îðéñţîƒîéð ðåţå åбöûţ åþþ þéŕƒöŕmåñçé åñð ûšåĝé îš šĥåŕéð ŵîţĥ Ĝööĝļé. Ţĥîš ðåţå ðöéš ñöţ îðéñţîƒý ýöû. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree]</string>
  <string name="agency_message_link">[Ļéåŕñ möŕé åţ\ñᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three four]</string>
  <string name="exposure_notifications_are_inactive">[Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš îš îñåçţîvé one two three four five six seven]</string>
  <string name="device_settings">[Ðévîçé šéţţîñĝš one two]</string>
  <string name="manage_storage">[Måñåĝé šţöŕåĝé one two]</string>
  <string name="location_off_warning">[Ţûŕñ öñ ýöûŕ ðévîçé\'š ļöçåţîöñ šéţţîñĝ ţö ĝéţ ñöţîƒîéð öƒ þöššîбļé éxþöšûŕé ţö ÇÖVÎÐ-19. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]</string>
  <string name="ble_off_warning">[Ţûŕñ öñ Бļûéţööţĥ ţö ĝéţ ñöţîƒîéð öƒ þöššîбļé éxþöšûŕé ţö ÇÖVÎÐ-19. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
  <string name="location_ble_off_warning">[Ţö ĝéţ ñöţîƒîéð öƒ þöššîбļé éxþöšûŕé ţö ÇÖVÎÐ-19, ţûŕñ öñ Бļûéţööţĥ &amp; ýöûŕ ðévîçé\'š ļöçåţîöñ šéţţîñĝ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen]</string>
  <string name="storage_low_warning">[Fŕéé ûþ šţöŕåĝé öñ ýöûŕ þĥöñé ţö ĝéţ ñöţîƒîéð öƒ þöššîбļé éxþöšûŕé ţö ÇÖVÎÐ-19. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
  <string name="not_in_allowlist_warning">[Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš îš ñö ļöñĝéŕ åvåîļåбļé îñ ýöûŕ ŕéĝîöñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
  <string name="hw_not_supported_warning">[Ţĥîš ðévîçé ðöéšñ\’ţ šûþþöŕţ Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš. Šéé ᐅ%1$sᐊ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
  <string name="device_requirements_link_text">[ðévîçé ŕéqûîŕéméñţš one two three]</string>
  <string name="switch_app_for_exposure_notifications">[Šŵîţçĥ åþþ ƒöŕ Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš¿ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
  <string name="focus_lost_warning">[Ýöû çåñ ûšé öñļý öñé Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš åþþ öñ ýöûŕ ðévîçé åţ å ţîmé.\ñ\ñÐö ýöû ŵåñţ ţö šŵîţçĥ ţö ţĥé ᐅ%1$sᐊ åþþ¿ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen]</string>
  <string name="switch_app_for_exposure_notifications_action">[Šŵîţçĥ åþþ one two]</string>
  <string name="en_not_supported_warning">[Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš îš ñö ļöñĝéŕ åvåîļåбļé. ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
  <string name="user_profile_not_supported_warning">[Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš îšñ\’ţ åvåîļåбļé öñ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé. Ţŕý åĝåîñ öñ ýöûŕ þéŕšöñåļ þŕöƒîļé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen]</string>
  <string name="onboarding_free_up_storage_title">[Fŕéé ûþ šţöŕåĝé šþåçé one two three four five]</string>
  <string name="reactivate_exposure_notification_app_subject">[Ĝéţ ÇÖVÎÐ-19 éxþöšûŕé åļéŕţš one two three four five six]</string>
  <string name="reactivate_exposure_notification_app_body">[ᐅ%1$sᐊ çåñ ñöţîƒý ýöû öƒ þöţéñţîåļ éxþöšûŕé ţö ÇÖVÎÐ-19 one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
  <string name="input_error_onset_date_past">[Ðåţé šĥöûļð öççûŕ ŵîţĥîñ ļåšţ ᐅ%1$sᐊ ðåýš öƒ ţöðåý\’š ðåţé one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
  <string name="input_error_onset_date_future">[Ðåţé öççûŕš îñ ţĥé ƒûţûŕé one two three four five six]</string>
  <string name="network_error_code_invalid">[Ţĥé véŕîƒîçåţîöñ çöðé ðöéšñ’ţ måţçĥ. Ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
  <string name="network_error_code_expired">[Ţĥé véŕîƒîçåţîöñ çöðé îš öûţ öƒ ðåţé. Çöñţåçţ ᐅ%1$sᐊ ƒöŕ å ñéŵ öñé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
  <string name="network_error_server_error">[Šöméţĥîñĝ ŵéñţ ŵŕöñĝ. Ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven]</string>
  <string name="network_error_unsupported_test_type">[Ţĥîš véŕîƒîçåţîöñ çöðé çåñ\'ţ бé ûšéð åţ ţĥîš ţîmé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
  <string name="share_error">[Ûñåбļé ţö šĥåŕé ţĥé ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ. Ţŕý åĝåîñ ļåţéŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
  <string name="generic_error_message">[Šöméţĥîñĝ ŵéñţ ŵŕöñĝ. Ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven]</string>
  <string name="code_error_already_submitted">[Çöðé ĥåš åļŕéåðý бééñ ûšéð ţö šĥåŕé ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
  <string name="gms_unavailable_error">[Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš ŕéqûîŕéš ţĥé ļåţéšţ véŕšîöñ öƒ Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕvîçéš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
  <string name="browser_unavailable_error">[Ţö vîéŵ ţĥîš çöñţéñţ, måķé šûŕé ýöû ĥåvé å ŕéçéñţ бŕöŵšéŕ îñšţåļļéð öñ ýöûŕ ðévîçé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]</string>
  <string name="settings_private_analytics_subtitle">[Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš åñåļýţîçš šĥåŕîñĝ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
  <string name="private_analytics_title">[Ĥéļþ ýöûŕ ĥéåļţĥ åûţĥöŕîţý ûñðéŕšţåñð ţĥé šþŕéåð öƒ ÇÖVÎÐ-19 one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
  <string name="private_analytics_subtitle">[Šĥåŕé Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš åñåļýţîçš ŵîţĥ ýöûŕ ĥéåļţĥ åûţĥöŕîţý one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
  <string name="private_analytics_footer">[Ţĥéšé åñåļýţîçš, šûçĥ åš ţĥé ñûmбéŕ öƒ ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš îñ ýöûŕ ŕéĝîöñ, ĥéļþ ĥéåļţĥ åûţĥöŕîţîéš ûñðéŕšţåñð ĥöŵ ÇÖVÎÐ-19 šþŕéåðš. Ţĥéý çåñ’ţ бé ŕéåð бý Ĝööĝļé åñð åŕé åĝĝŕéĝåţéð ƒöŕ ýöûŕ ĥéåļţĥ åûţĥöŕîţý šö ţĥéý çåñ’ţ бé ļîñķéð ţö ýöûŕ þĥöñé. ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight twentynine thirty thirtyone]</string>
  <string name="private_analytics_footer_onboarding">[Ţĥéšé åñåļýţîçš çåñ’ţ бé ŕéåð бý Ĝööĝļé åñð åŕé åĝĝŕéĝåţéð ƒöŕ ýöûŕ ĥéåļţĥ åûţĥöŕîţý šö ţĥéý çåñ’ţ бé ļîñķéð ţö ýöûŕ þĥöñé. ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty]</string>
  <string name="private_analytics_footer_learn_more">[Ļéåŕñ möŕé one two]</string>
  <string name="diagnosis_subtitle_template">[ᐅ%1$sᐊ öñ ᐅ%2$sᐊ one two three]</string>
  <string name="empty_share_history_body">[Ñö šĥåŕîñĝ ĥîšţöŕý one two three]</string>
  <string name="share_diagnosis_share_test_result_title">[Šĥåŕé ýöûŕ ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ ŵîţĥ ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three four five six seven]</string>
  <string name="share_diagnosis_share_test_result_subtitle">[Ţĥåñķ ýöû ƒöŕ ĥéļþîñĝ ţö šţöþ ÇÖVÎÐ-19. one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
  <string name="share_diagnosis_share_test_result_body">[Ŵĥéñ ýöû šĥåŕé ýöûŕ ŕéšûļţ, ýöû çåñ åļšö çĥööšé ţö šĥåŕé ŵĥéñ ýöûŕ šýmþţömš šţåŕţéð. Ţĥîš îñƒöŕmåţîöñ çåñ ĥéļþ šţöþ ţĥé šþŕéåð öƒ ÇÖVÎÐ-19 åñð šåvé ļîvéš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree]</string>
  <string name="sms_intercept_notice_title">[Ŵĥåţ\'š ñéŵ one two]</string>
  <string name="sms_intercept_notice_content">[Îƒ ýöû ŕéçéîvé åñ ŠMŠ ŵîţĥ ýöûŕ ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ, ýöû måý ĝéţ å ñöţîƒîçåţîöñ åšķîñĝ ýöû ţö šĥåŕé ýöûŕ ðîåĝñöšîš îñ éxþöšûŕé ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš. Ýöû çåñ ðîšåбļé ţĥîš åñý ţîmé îñ šéţţîñĝš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive]</string>
  <string name="share_upload_title">[Šĥåŕé ýöûŕ ţéšţ ŕéšûļţ ţö þŕöţéçţ ýöûŕ çömmûñîţý one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
  <string name="share_upload_test_result_source_description">[Ŕéšûļţš ŵéŕé šéñţ бý ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three four five]</string>
  <string name="share_upload_symptoms_subtitle">[Šýmþţömš бéĝåñ öñ one two three]</string>
  <string name="share_upload_symptoms_date_fixed_description">[Šýmþţöm ðåţé îš þŕövîðéð бý ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three four five six seven]</string>
  <string name="share_upload_skip_choice">[Šķîþ one]</string>
  <string name="share_upload_travel_subtitle">[Ţŕåvéļ ĥîšţöŕý one two]</string>
  <string name="travel_history_travelled_recently_choice">[Ţŕåvéļéð îñ ţĥé þåšţ 14 ðåýš one two three four five six]</string>
  <string name="travel_history_no_travel_choice">[Î ðîðñ\'ţ ţŕåvéļ one two]</string>
  <string name="share_upload_select_a_date_choice">[Šéļéçţ å ðåţé one two]</string>
  <string name="share_upload_status_subtitle">[ÇÖVÎÐ-19 šţåţûš one two]</string>
  <string name="share_upload_status_confirmed">[Þöšîţîvé one]</string>
  <string name="share_upload_status_negative">[Ñéĝåţîvé one]</string>
  <string name="share_upload_status_likely">[Ļîķéļý one]</string>
  <string name="share_diagnosis_progress_tracker">[Šţéþ ᐅ%1$dᐊ öƒ ᐅ%2$dᐊ one two three four]</string>
  <string name="see_history_device_authentication_title">[Véŕîƒý îţ\'š ýöû one two]</string>
  <string name="update_app_dialog_title">[Ûþðåţé ýöûŕ åþþ one two]</string>
  <string name="update_app_dialog_content">[Ûþðåţé ţö ţĥé ļåţéšţ véŕšîöñ öƒ Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš ţö ƒîñîšĥ šĥåŕîñĝ ýöûŕ ţéšţ ŕéšûļţš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen]</string>
  <string name="btn_update">[Ûþðåţé one]</string>
  <string name="try_again_later_error_message">[Šöméţĥîñĝ ŵéñţ ŵŕöñĝ. Ţŕý åĝåîñ îñ å ƒéŵ ĥöûŕš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
  <string name="en_turndown_for_area_title">[Ýöûŕ Ĥéåļţĥ Åûţĥöŕîţý ñö ļöñĝéŕ šûþþöŕţš Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
  <string name="en_turndown_title">[Éxþöšûŕé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš ĥåš бééñ ţûŕñéð öƒƒ one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
</resources>
